Guide to the Gerhard Casper, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0672
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- President's records, 1996-1997; Accession ARCH-1999-171
  - Sponsored Projects, 5/9/96-8/11/97; R 1 (Box 14)
  - Stanford Center for Chicano Research, 3/24/97-8/14/97; R 1.3 (Box 14)
  - Institute for Research-Women/Gender, 11/1/96-8/22/97; R 1.8 (Box 14)
  - Institute for International Studies IIS, 9/23/96-8/29/97; R 1.12 (Box 14)
  - Division of Lab Ånimal Medicine, 5/20/97 only; R 1.14 (Box 14)
  - Research Policies (R2 reissued to BioX), 33872; R 2.0 (Box 14)
  - Institutional Review Board for Human Subs, 11/6/96-12/15/97; R 5 (Box 14)
  - Stanford Leadership Institute, 10/7/96-4/3/97; R 7 (Box 14)
  - The Science Coalition, 11/21/96-5/29/97; R 8 (Box 14)
  - Student Misc, 10/1/96-6/5/97; ST 1 (Box 15)
  - Student Groups Misc, 9/24/96-8/6/97; ST 1.1 (Box 15)
  - ASSU Assoc Students of SU, 9/25/96-7/16/97; ST 2 (Box 15)
  - The Stanford Band, 2/10/97 only; ST 3.4 (Box 15)
  - Bechtel International Center, 9/5/96-5/21/97; ST 3.5 (Box 15)
  - KZSU Student Radio, 4/18/97 only; ST 3.18 (Box 15)
  - Haas Public Service Center, 9/18/96-6/25/97; ST 3.29 (Box 15)
  - John Gardner Fellowship, 2/6/97 only; ST 3.29/1 (Box 15)
  - Campus Compact, 9/9/96-8/29/97; ST 3.35 (Box 15)
  - Scholarships, 9/19/96-10/31/96; ST 7 (Box 15)
  - Asian Pacific Scholarship Program, 9/19/96-8/21/97; ST 7.1 (Box 15)
  - Student/Parent Corresp's, 10/13/96-8/21/97; ST 8 (Box 15)
- President's records, 1997-1998; Accession ARCH-2000-203
  - Provost's Office, 9/24/97 - 2/3/98; AA 1 (Box 1)
  - Presidential Search Committee, AA 1.2 (Box 1)
  - Dean of the Chapel - Academic, 12/1/97 - 8/26/1998; AA 1.8 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Graduate Fellowships, 9/5/97 - 8/29/98; AA 1.12 (Box 1)
  - Graduate Students/Studies, Issues, 9/22/97 - 6/10/98; AA 1.13 (Box 1)
  - Emeriti, 9/3/97 - 8/28/98; AA 2.2 (Box 1)
  - Affirmative Action, Faculty/Staff, AA 2.3.3 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Development (Faculty Affairs, Misc.), *5/29/97 from Design Div./Re: Ed Carryer; AA 2.7 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Development (Faculty Affairs, Misc.), 9/22/97 - 6/15/98; AA 2.7 (Box 1)
  - Fellows of the University, 1/27/98 - 5/29/98; AA 2.9 (Box 1)
  - Teaching & Research Assist/Assoc., 11/18/97 - 1/27/98; AA 2.11 (Box 1)
  - Undergraduate Studies/Issues, 9/3/97 - 6/30/98; AA 3 (Box 1)
  - Accreditation Issues / Very General, 1/30/98 - 7/6/98; AA 3.4 (Box 1)
  - US News/World Rpt. Rankings/Ratings, 9/1/97 - 8/31/98; AA 3.5 (Box 1)
  - Ideals/Values (West Culture requirement), AA 3.5.1 (Box 1)
  - Continuing Studies, 10/22/97 - 5/4/98; AA 3.6 (Box 1)
  - Television, Cable, CH51, etc., 9/8/97 - 6/15/98; AA 3.9.1 (Box 1)
  - Summer Programs, et al, 9/8/97 - 5/25/98; AA 3.16 (Box 1)
  - Sophomore Seminars, 9/2/97 - 6/4/98; AA 3.18.2 (Box 1)
  - School of Humanities & Science, *6/19/97 From: Morris Graves/Re: Fix term appt.; AA 4.1 (Box 1)
  - School of Humanities & Science, * 8/14/92 From: Ewart Thomas/RE: Fundraising; AA 4.1 (Box 1)
  - School of Humanities & Science, 9/2/97 - 8/31/98; AA 4.1 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Humanities Center, 9/16/97 - 7/28/98; AA 4.1.1/2 (Box 1)
  - Applied Physics, Dept of, 9/10/97 - 7/22/98; AA 4.1.8 (Box 1)
  - Art, Dept of, 2/5/98 - 3/29/98; AA 4.1.9 (Box 1)
  - Chemistry, Dept of, 1/15/98 - 8/12/98; AA 4.1.13 (Box 1)
  - Dance, Dept of, 5/4/98 - 8/31/98; AA 4.1.16 (Box 1)
  - Computer Science, Dept of, 9/19/97 - 7/21/98; AA 4.1.17 (Box 1)
  - Drama, Dept of, 9/15/97 - 8/19/98; AA. 4.1.18 (Box 1)
  - Economics, Dept of, 9/12/97 - 8/14/98; AA 4.1.20 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Inst. for Economic Policy Research (SIEPR), 9/7/97 - 6/3/98; AA 4.1.20/1 (Box 1)
  - English, Dept of, 9/3/97 - 8/12/1998; AA 4.1.21 (Box 1)
  - French & Italian, Dept of, 9/16/97 - 7/1/98; AA 4.1.22 (Box 1)
  - German, Dept of, 9/26/97 only; AA 4.1.24 (Box 1)
  - History, Dept of, 10/18/97 - 7/28/98; AA 4.1.25 (Box 2)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (HMS), 9/97 - 7/16/98; AA 4.1.28 (Box 2)
  - Music, Dept of, 9/2/97 - 8/21/98; AA 4.1.29 (Box 2)
  - Athletics, Dept of, * 8/7/92 Frm: Ted Leland/RE: Fundraising; AA 4.1.30 (Box 2)
  - Football Games, Tyrone Willingham - Rose Bowl, etc., 10/3/97 - 4/21/968; AA 4.1.30/1 (Box 2)
  - Philosophy, Dept. of, 11/3/97 - 3/18/98; AA 4.1.32 (Box 2)
  - Physics, Dept of, 9/4/97 - 7/22/1998; AA 4.1.33 (Box 2)
  - Political Science Department, *5/14/97 - From: Terry Karl/Re: Reappt. / *6/3/97 From: Barry Weingast RE thanks.; AA 4.1.34 (Box 2)
  - Political Science Department, 10/9/97 - 4/29/98; AA 4.1.34 (Box 2)
  - Psychology, Dept of, 3/17/98 - 4/16/98; AA 4.1.35 (Box 2)
  - Stanford Center for Research on Economic Dev & Policy, 11/4/97 - 8/26/98; AA 4.1.48 (Box 2)
  - (previously Food Research Institute) (Box 2)
  - Graduate School of Business, 9/1/97 - 6/25/98; AA 4.2 (Box 2)
  - Earth Sciences, School of, 9/24/97 - 7/2/98; AA 4.3 (Box 2)
  - Engineering, School of, * 8/15/92 From: James Gibbons/RE: Fund Raising; AA 4.4 (Box 2)
  - Engineering, School of, 9/10/97 - 3/8/98; AA 4.4 (Box 2)
  - Engineering, School of, 3/20/98 - 8/25/98; AA 4.4 (Box 2)
  - Education, School of, 9/30/97 - 8/21/98; AA 4.5 (Box 2)
  - School of Medicine [This is a dead code for the current year, but note that there is a document from a much earlier year], * 8/13/92 From David Korn/RE: Fundraising Needs; AA 4.6 (Box 2)
  - Hoover Institute, * 9/4/92 From: John Raisian/Re: Fund Raising; AA 4.9 (Box 2)
  - Hoover Institute, 9/8/97 - 11/21/97; AA 4.9 (Box 2)
  - Hoover Institute, 12/1/97 - 2/16/98; AA 4.9 (Box 2)
  - Hoover Institute, 3/3/98 - 5/26/98; AA 4.9 (Box 2)
  - Hoover Institute, 6/2/98 - 8/31/98; AA 4.9 (Box 2)
  - Sweden Stuff related to Learning Lab, 11/20/97 - 8/20/98; AA 4.10.4 (Box 2)
  - Center for International Security and Cooperation (formerly known as CISAC)- From: John Lewis/Re: Mtg ~US/China, * 8/8/95, 9/12/97 - 7/30/98; AA 4.10.6 (Box 3)
  - Center for Latin American Studies, 10/7/97 - 8/4/98; AA 4.11 (Box 3)
  - Center for Russian & East European Studies, 11/5/97 - 4/1/98; AA 4.11.1 (Box 3)
  - Libraries at Stanford (general catch-all), 9/13/97 - 8/11/98; AA 4.12 (Box 3)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center (SLAC), 9/4/97 - 4/9/98; AA 4.13 (Box 3)
  - Center for the Study of Language and Information, 9/5/97 - 6/21/98; AA 4.14.1 (Box 3)
  - Law School From: Jacqueline Wender/RE: response to Ken Malpass, * 2/28/97; AA 4.15 (Box 3)
  - Information Technology Service (ITS), 10/1/97 - 8/31/98; AA 4.22 (Box 3)
  - Awards/Prizes, Misc., 9/22/97 - 6/24/98; AA 5 (Box 3)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 34493; AA 5.2 (Box 3)
  - Presidential Scholars, 10/15/97 - 5/28/98; AA 5.3 (Box 3)
  - Sterling, Wallace Award, 3/23/1998 only; AA 5.5 (Box 3)
  - Gold Spike Award (for outstanding volunteers), AA 5.26 (Box 3)
  - Grants, Scholarships, Misc., 10/10/97 - 8/31/98; AA 6 (Box 3)
  - Fellowships, Misc/General Information, 9/19/97 - 8/31/98; AA 8 (Box 3)
  - Fullbright Fellowship/Scholarship, 12/15/97 - 7/28/98; AA 8.16 (Box 3)
  - Guggenheim Memorial Fellowship, 4/9/98 - only; AA 8.17 (Box 3)
  - Knight Fellowships/Foundation, 8/31/97 - 5/5/98; AA 8.25 (Box 3)
  - Terman Fellowship, 10/3/97 - 2/5/98; AA 8.30 (Box 3)
  - Tanner Fellowship, 9/8/97 - 8/28/98; AA 9.19 (Box 3)
  - Endowed Chairs/Professorships, Miscellaneous, 9/4/97 - 4/29/98; AA 10 (Box 3)
  - Stanford, Miscelleneous, Stanfordiana, 9/1/97 - 8/24/98; AD 1 (Box 3)
  - Historical Society, Stanford, 1/5/98 - 5/29/98; AD 1.2 (Box 3)
  - ROTC, 1/5/98 - 6/18/98; AD 2.26 (Box 3)
  - Honor Code/Fundamental Standard, 9/22/97 - 5/26/98; AD 3.10 (Box 3)
  - President's Office, 9/97-12/97; AD 4.0 (Box 3)
  - President's Office, 1/98-6/98; AD 4.0 (Box 3)
  - President's Office, 7/98-8/98; AD 4.0 (Box 3)
  - Presidential Lecture Symposium Human & Arts (PLSHA), 10/97-2/98; AD 4.2 (Box 3)
  - Presidential Lecture Symposium Human & Arts (PLSHA), 2/98-7/98; AD 4.2 (Box 3)
  - President's House, Staff, Car, 9/15/97 - 7/29/98; AD 4.7 (Box 3)
  - University Cabinet, * 2/28/96 From: Lowell Price; AD 4.13 (Box 4)
  - University Cabinet, 11/97 - 5/98; AD 4.13 (Box 4)
  - General Counsel, 9/16/97 - 2/23/98; AD 4.19 (Box 4)
  - General Counsel, 3/17/98 - 4/28/98; AD 4.19 (Box 4)
  - General Counsel, 5/13/98 - 6/27/98; AD 4.19 (Box 4)
  - General Counsel, 7/8/98 - 8/26/98; AD 4.19 (Box 4)
  - General Correspondences, 9/18/97 - 4/27/98; AD 4.20 (Box 4)
  - News Clippings, 1/15/98 - 7/24/98 only; AD 4.20.1 (Box 4)
  - Condolence Letters, 9/7/97 - 8/18/98; AD 4.20.2 (Box 4)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 12/21/97 - 7/8/98; AD 4.20.3 (Box 4)
  - Letters of Appreciation, 12/24/97 - 7/3/98; AD 4.20.4/1 (Box 4)
  - Invitations, 9/5/97 - 12/18/97; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 4)
  - Invitations, 1/2/98 - 8/31/98; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 4)
  - Casper's Resignation, AD 4.20.4/3 (Box 4)
  - Nonsense, 9/7/97 - 9/26/97; AD 4.20.5 (Box 4)
  - Nonsense, * 7/7/97 Frm: Huy Vo/Re: His $4MM?; AD 4.20.5 (Box 4)
  - Nonsense, 10/3/97 - 11/14/97; AD 4.20.5 (Box 4)
  - Nonsense, 11/14/97 - 5/6/98; AD 4.20.5 (Box 4)
  - Nonsense, 5/8/98 - 8/24/98; AD 4.20.5 (Box 4)
  - Routine Recommendation Letters (search letters), 9/3/97 - 2/27/98; AD 4.20.6 (Box 4)
  - Routine Recommendation Letters (search letters), 3/2/98 - 8/31/98; AD 4.20.6 (Box 4)
  - Recommendations Letters (Students), 9/5/97 - 8/7/98; AD 4.20.6/1 (Box 4)
  - Complaint Letters, 11/11/97 - 8/10/98; AD 4.20.7 (Box 4)
  - Solicitation Letters (General), 9/97 - 8/98; AD 4.20.8 (Box 5)
  - University Communications, *6/25/97 From: Geoff Cox/Re: External Review; AD 4.22 (Box 5)
  - University Communications, 10/10/97 - 8/14/98; AD 4.22 (Box 5)
  - Office of Campus Relations, 9/20/97 - 7/14/98; AD 6 (Box 5)
  - Admissions, * 1/23/96; 3/14/96; 9/23/96 all from Becky D'Angelo; AD 8.1 (Box 5)
  - Admissions, 9/8/97 - 8/31/98; AD 8.1 (Box 5)
  - Admissions, AD 8.1 (Box 5)
  - Student Affairs, Dean of, * 6/5/97 From: Mary Edmonds/Re: Hazing; AD 8.8 (Box 5)
  - Student Affairs, Dean of, 9/3/97 - 8/26/98; AD 8.8 (Box 5)
  - Cowell Student Health Center, AD 8.9 (Box 5)
  - Stanford in Washington D.C., 10/31/97 - 4/24/98; AD 8.10.1 (Box 5)
  - Overseas Studies Programs, 10/19/97 - 8/19/98; AD 8.11 (Box 5)
  - Financial Aid, 9/8/97 - 7/20/98; AD 8.12 (Box 5)
  - Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, Housing, 9/5/97 - 8/13/98; AD 8.18 (Box 5)
  - Hanna-Honeycomb House, 10/17/97 - 3/18/98; AD 8.18.2 (Box 5)
  - Lake House, AD 8.18.3 (Box 5)
  - Buck Estate, AD 8.18.4 (Box 5)
  - Housing/Dining Services-Students, 9/11/97 - 8/29/98; AD 8.18.11 (Box 5)
  - Housing/Dining Services-Students, AD 8.18.11 (Box not specified)
  - Residential Education, 9/2/97 - 8/4/98; AD 8.18.13 (Box 6)
  - Registrar - Bursar, 9/3/97 - 8/17/98; AD 8.21 (Box 6)
  - Multi-Cultural Development, 12/12/97 - 5/28/98; AD 9.6 (Box 6)
  - Affirmative Action, Student, 10/14/97 - 8/14/98; AD 9.6.3 (Box 6)
  - Employee and Personnel Relations, *9/11/95 only frm Katrina Jaggears; AD 10 (Box 6)
  - Employee and Personnel Relations, 9/2/97 - 8/18/98; AD 10 (Box 6)
  - Employment Inquiries/Requests, * 8/25/97 - From: John Baugh/Re: V. Chan of Mass, Amherst; AD 10.1 (Box 6)
  - Employment Inquiries/Requests, 9/10/97 - 8/28/98; AD 10.1 (Box 6)
  - Committee for Art, 9/4/97 - 8/26/98; AD 10.7.4 (Box 6)
  - United Stanford Employees (USE), AD 10.7.8 (Box 6)
  - Grievances - Student, 10/1/97 - 7/29/98; AD 10.8.10/3 (Box 6)
  - Retirement, 11/13/97 - 7/1/98; AD 10.8.17 (Box 6)
  - Salaries, 9/25/97 - 5/28/98; AD 10.8.19 (Box 6)
  - Operations and Maintenance, 10/3/97 - 2/5/98; AD 11.4 (Box 6)
  - Environmental Safety Facility, 9/1/97 - 8/24/98; AD 11.4.1 (Box 6)
  - Police Services/Campus Security, 10/1/97 - 12/11/97; AD 11.6 (Box 6)
  - Stanford Events, 10/28/97 - 6/25/98; AD 11.7.5/1 (Box 6)
  - Lively Arts at Stanford, 10/13/97 - 6/5/98; AD 11.7.5/2 (Box 6)
  - Freshmen Orientation, 9/1/97 - 8/11/98; AD 11.7.7 (Box 6)
  - Media - All Forms - External, 9/9/97 - 7/28/98; AD 11.8 (Box 6)
  - Stanford University Press, 9/5/97 - 7/21/98; AD 11.8.9 (Box 6)
  - Surveys, Studies, Questionnaires, 12/22/97 - 7/31/98; AD 11.8.10 (Box 6)
  - Media, Internal, 9/3/97 - 8/10/98; AD 11.8.11 (Box 6)
  - Business and Finance, 9/16/97 - 8/31/98; AD 12.2 (Box 6)
  - Administrative Resources, 9/5/97 - 8/26/98; AD 12.2/3 (Box 6)
  - Stanford Management Company, 9/9/97 - 8/31/98; AD 12.3 (Box 6)
  - Internal Auditing-From: Steve Jung/Re: Stern Renov. Proj., * 8/27/97; AD 12.4 (Box 6)
  - Internal Auditing, 9/4/97 - 8/21/98; AD 12.4 (Box 6)
  - Budget (Budget Group), 9/11/97 - 8/18/98; AD 12.5 (Box 6)
  - Tuition, 10/17/97 - 6/9/1998; AD 12.5.4 (Box 6)
  - Institutional Planning: Geoff Cox, * 6/11/97 From: Geoff Cox/Re: Facilities Project; AD 12.6 (Box 7)
  - Institutional Planning: Geoff Cox, *7/8/97 From: Geoff Cox/Re: FU to 6-27 mtg; AD 12.6 (Box 7)
  - Institutional Planning: Geoff Cox, *8/19/97 - From Geoff Cox/Re: Reorg of Fac. Proj.; AD 12.6 (Box 7)
  - Institutional Planning: Geoff Cox, 10/24/97 - 8/3/98; AD 12.6 (Box 7)
  - Insurance, Risk Management, 3/11/98 - 7/23/98; AD 12.8 (Box 7)
  - Vice President for Development, 9/10/97 - 8/10/98; AD 12.10 (Box 7)
  - Office of Development, * 8/19/97 Frm: John Ford RE: Assoc VP&Dir Univ. Develop; AD 12.10.1 (Box 7)
  - President Discretionary Allocation, 8/20/98 - 8/25/98 only; AD 12.10.2 (Box 7)
  - Student Fund Raising, 1/29/98 - 6/11/98; AD 12.10.2/1 (Box 7)
  - President's Fund, 9/5/97 - 8/24/98; AD 12.10.2/2 (Box 7)
  - The Stanford Fund, 9/9/97 - 8/28/98; AD 12.10.2/3 (Box 7)
  - Matching Gifts, 9/8/97 - 6/12/98; AD 12.10.2/4 (Box 7)
  - Development, Events, 9/26/97 - 5/1/98; AD 12.10.2/5 (Box 7)
  - Donor Relations, 10/2/97 - 8/25/98; AD 12.10.2/7 (Box 7)
  - Asian Relations, General, 9/2/97 - 8/24/98; AD 12.10.2/9 (Box 7)
  - Technology Licensing/Patents/Copyrights, 9/5/97 - 8/20/98; AD 12.11 (Box 7)
  - Land and Buildings, General catch all, 9/25/97 - 8/27/98; AD 12.14 (Box 7)
  - Wattis Room, *10/29/96 - 8/27/97 and 9/2/97 - 8/31/98; also AD 12.14 (Box 7)
  - Art Gallery & Museums, 9/16/97 - 8/31/98; AD 12.14.7/1 (Box 8)
  - Bookstore, Stanford, 3/26/98 - 8/21/98; AD 12.14.7/5 (Box 8)
  - Bookstore, Stanford, AD 12.14.7/5 (Box 8)
  - Bookstore, Stanford, AD 12.14.7/5 (Box 8)
  - Bookstore, Stanford, AD 12.14.7/5 (Box 8)
  - Facilities / Planning / Univ. Architect, 9/3/97 - 8/19/98; AD 12.14.7/29 (Box 8)
  - Facilities / Planning / Univ. Architect, * 10/12/93 From John Raisian/Re: Asbestos; AD 12.14.7/29 (Box 8)
  - Faculty Club, 9/17/97 - 4/25/98; AD 12.14.7/30 (Box 8)
  - Jasper Ridge Biological Experimental Area (space), 11/19/97 - 7/28/98; AD 12.14.7/43 (Box 8)
  - Memorial Church, 10/17/97 - 8/31/98; AD 12.14.7/50 (Box 8)
  - Parking/Transportation, 11/5/97 - 5/29/98; AD 12.14.7/53 (Box 8)
  - Tressider Memorial Union (TMU), AD 12.14.7/64 (Box 8)
  - Visitors to campus, 11/20/97 - 8/24/98; AD 13.10 (Box 8)
  - Conferences, Misc., 9/9/97 - 8/4/98; AD 13.10.1 (Box 8)
  - Industrial Relations, 11/18/1997 only; AD 15 (Box 8)
  - Alumni Relations, * 3/3/97 - From: Ogletree/Re: Minority Task Force; AL 1 (Box 8)
  - Parent's Club (formerly known as "Mother's Club"), 9/5/97 - 4/23/98; AL 1.1/1 (Box 8)
  - Alumni Correspondence (General - Not Parent/Student), 9/1/97 - 8/26/98; AL 1.3 (Box 8)
  - Alumni Letter Campaign/ Stanford Magazine Classnote, AL 1.3.1 (Box 8)
  - Annual Graduate Mailing, 9/1/97 - 8/31/98; AL 1.4 (Box 8)
  - Alumni Conference/Homecoming, 9/10/97 - 7/6/98; AL 1.7 (Box 8)
  - Alumni Association [includes one letter from 1995 from Duncan Beardsley/Nat'l Geogph map], 9/17/97 - 7/21/98; AL 3 (Box 8)
  - SAA - 2000 (Stanford Alumni Association), 9/24/97 - 8/31/98; AL 3.1 (Box 8)
  - Alumni Giving (OOD), 9/30/97 - 8/8/98; AL 5 (Box 9)
  - Board of Trustees, 9/97-1/98; B 1 (Box 9)
  - Board of Trustees, 1/98-6/98; B 1 (Box 9)
  - Board of Trustees, 6/98-8/98; B 1 (Box 9)
  - Board of Trustees Appointments, 12/7/97 - 8/17/98; B 12 (Box 9)
  - Board of Trustees Committees, 9/8/97 - 8/20/98; B 14 (Box 9)
  - Trustee Committee on Land & Use Building Campus Plng, 1/28/98 - 6/2/98; B 14.6 (Box 9)
  - Academic Council, 10/22/97 - 5/28/98; C 1 (Box 9)
  - Academic Council - Senate, * 1/30/97 - From: Charles Cole/Re: 95-96 Assets of Coun.; C 2 (Box 9)
  - Academic Council - Senate, 9/18/97 - 12/21/97; C 2 (Box 9)
  - Academic Council - Senate, 34306; C 2 (Box 9)
  - Academic Council - Senate, 12/22/97 - 2/19/98; C 2 (Box 9)
  - Academic Council - Senate, 3/9/98 - 4/6/98; C 2 (Box 9)
  - Academic Council - Senate, 4/9/98 - 4/16/98; C 2 (Box 9)
  - Academic Council - Senate, 4/17/98 - 4/29/98; C 2 (Box 9)
  - Academic Council - Senate, 5/14/98 - 6/26/98; C 2 (Box 9)
  - Academic Council - Advisory Board, 9/25/97 - 8/21/98; C 3 (Box 9)
  - Academic Council - Steering Committee - STC, 10/15/97 - 11/6/97; C 4.1 (Box 9)
  - Commission on Technology in Teaching and Learning, 9/15/97 - 5/22/98; C 5.7.2 (Box 9)
  - University Committees, 9/19/97 - 8/7/98; C 6 (Box 9)
  - Committee of Fifteen, C 6.1 (Box 9)
  - General Gov't Info., * 2/10/97 From Mike Hudnall RE: Land use consideration; G 1 (Box 9)
  - General Gov't Info., 10/25/97 - 8/27/98; G 1 (Box 9)
  - Performing Arts Center - [Government Misc.], G1 PAC (Box 9)
  - California State Government, 9/2/97 - 8/24/98; G 1.2 (Box 9)
  - Environmental Protection Agency, 9/15/1997 only; G 2.3 (Box 9)
  - U.S. Governmental Relations, 9/11/97 - 8/24/98; G 3 (Box 10)
  - Department of Defense (DoD), 12/8/97 - 7/29/98; G 3.7 (Box 10)
  - Department of Energy (DoE), 10/3/97 only; G 3.7.2 (Box 10)
  - National Aeronautics & Space Administration (NASA), 12/23/97 - 4/23/98; G 3.7.4 (Box 10)
  - Health & Human Services, Office of Civil Rights -From: David O. Stewart RE: Revival of PATH II Audit Process / Frm: Jordan Cohen RE: PATH Initiative / Frm: Larry Horton RE: CFR Update, * 8/21/97; G 3.8.1 (Box 10)
  - Health & Human Services, Office of Civil Rights, 9/5/97 - 6/29/98; G 3.8.1 (Box 10)
  - National Institutes of Health (NIH), 10/24/97 - 2/13/98; G 3.8.2 (Box 10)
  - Department of Education, U.S. (USDE), 11/17/97 - 8/25/98; G 3.8.3 (Box 10)
  - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), 8/3/98 - 8/25/98 only; G 3.18.1 (Box 10)
  - NSF - National Science Foundation, 9/9/97 - 8/31/98; G 3.19 (Box 10)
  - Local Government / Local Business, 9/23/97 - 5/1/98; G 4 (Box 10)
  - Foreign Government Relations, misc., 10/3/97 - 8/28/98; G 5 (Box 10)
  - CA Institute for Federal Policy Research, 9/18/97 - 8/28/98; G 7 (Box 10)
  - Stanford in Government, 9/9/97 - 7/15/98; G 8 (Box 10)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 9/3/97 - 8/27/1998; G 10 (Box 10)
  - United Nations, 11/27/97 only; G 12 (Box 10)
  - Kaiser, *1/96 - 9/96; SHS 3 (Box 11)
  - Special / Newco/ UCSF, *9/9/96 - 1/22/97; SHS 3 (Box 11)
  - Stanford Health Care Board of Directors [end 1-31-97; use SHS 15], *1/27/97 only; SHS 3 * UCSF (Box 11)
  - Meeting of the Selectors, *12/20/96 only; SHS 3 *UCSF (Box 11)
  - USHC [UCSF-SU Health Care], *2/3/97 - 2/20/97; SHS 15 (Box 11)
  - USHC [UCSF-SU Health Care], *2/24/97 - 4/16/97; SHS 15 (Box 11)
  - USHC [UCSF-SU Health Care], *4/16/97 - 4/30/97; SHS 15 (Box 11)
  - USHC [UCSF-SU Health Care], *5/2/97 - 6/13/97; SHS 15 (Box 11)
  - USHC [UCSF-SU Health Care], *6/13/97 - 8/5/97; SHS 15 (Box 11)
  - USHC [UCSF-SU Health Care], *8/6/97 - 8/29/97; SHS 15 (Box 11)
  - USHC [UCSF-SU Health Care], SHS 15 (Box 11)
  - USHC [UCSF-SU Health Care], 9/3/97 - 9/4/97; SHS 15 (Box 11)
  - USHC [UCSF-SU Health Care], 9/8/97 - 9/15/97; SHS 15 (Box 11)
  - USHC [UCSF-SU Health Care], 9/16/97 only; SHS 15 (Box 11)
  - USHC [UCSF-SU Health Care], 9/16/97 - 10/14/97; SHS 15 (Box 11)
  - USHC [UCSF-SU Health Care], 10/21/97 - 10/28/97; SHS 15 (Box 11)
  - UCSF-SHC Merger, 10/7/97 - 1/7/98; UCSF/SHC-1 (Box 11)
  - UCSF-SHC Merger, 1/12/98 - 1/27/98; UCSF/SHC-1 (Box 11)
  - UCSF-SHC Merger, 2/5/98 only; UCSF/SHC-1 (Box 11)
  - UCSF-SHC Merger, 2/6/98 - 2/25/98; UCSF/SHC-1 (Box 11)
  - UCSF-SHC Merger, 3/2/98 - 6/23/98; UCSF/SHC-1 (Box 11)
  - UCSF-SHC Merger, 7/1/98 - 8/31/98; UCSF/SHC-1 (Box 11)
  - There are later documents in code SHS 3* NEWCO/UCSF up to 2/1/97. Then use SHS 15 until 11/1/97. The final code became UCSF/SHC-1. Sorry for the confusion!! (per Leigh Norling). (Box 11)
  - Hospital Auxillary, 11/12/97 - 8/12/98; SHS 1 (Box 12)
  - Administration - Special File on Dr. Kiran Bhatt, *5/16/97 - 5/13/98/ok to archive per Ingrid.; SHS 3 (Box 12)
  - Hospital Administration, 9/26/97 - 7/13/98; SHS 3 (Box 12)
  - Hospital Administration, *9/2/96 - 12/4/96; SHS 3 (Box 12)
  - Hospital Administration, * 1/20/97 - 8/26/97; SHS 3 (Box 12)
  - Hospital Board of Directors, 34237; SHS 4 (Box 12)
  - Hospital Board of Directors, 9/27/97 - 10/31/97; SHS 4 (Box 12)
  - Hospital Board of Directors, *9/6/96 - 12/6/96; SHS 4 (Box 12)
  - Hospital Board of Directors, *12/26/96 only; SHS 4 (Box 12)
  - Hospital Board of Directors, *1/16/97 - 2/3/97; SHS 4 (Box 12)
  - Hospital Board of Directors, *2/7/97 - 4/10/97; SHS 4 (Box 12)
  - Hospital Board of Directors, *7/14/97 - 8/15/97; SHS 4 (Box 12)
  - Lucille Salter Packard Children's Hospital, 10/31/97 - 12/1/97; SHS 7 (Box 12)
  - Lucille Salter Packard Children's Hospital, 12/4/97 - 7/17/98; SHS 7 (Box 12)
  - Lucille Salter Packard Children's Hospital, *9/9/1996 - 9/12/96; SHS 7 (Box 12)
  - Lucille Salter Packard Children's Hospital, *9/19/96 - 7/14/97; SHS 7 (Box 12)
  - Medical Organizations (Miscellaneous), *4/19/97- 8/7/98; SHS 8 (Box 12)
  - Howard Hughes Medical Institute, * 9/12/96 - 6/3/97; SHS 9 (Box 12)
  - Howard Hughes Medical Institute, 9/11/97 - 6/22/98; SHS 9 (Box 12)
  - Other Affiliated Hospitals, Centers and Clinics, *2/12/97 - 6/30/97; SHS 13 (Box 12)
  - Other Affiliated Hospitals, Centers and Clinics, 9/2/97 - 8/17/98; SHS 13 (Box 12)
  - Patient Relations, *9/3/96 - 8/27/97; SHS 14 (Box 12)
  - Patient Relations, 9/3/97 - 8/17/98; SHS 14 (Box 12)
  - School of Medicine Administration, *10/20/95 only; M 1 (Box 12)
  - School of Medicine Administration, 9/2/97 - 12/16/97; M 1 (Box 12)
  - School of Medicine Administration, 12/17/97 - 4/9/98; M 1 (Box 12)
  - School of Medicine Administration, 4/10/98 - 6/3/98; M 1 (Box 12)
  - School of Medicine Administration, 6/3/98 - 8/28/98; M 1 (Box 12)
  - Medical School Development, *9/5/96 - 2/28/97; M 2 (Box 13)
  - Medical School Development, 1/23/98 - 8/17/98; M 2 (Box 13)
  - Misc. Medical School Departments, 9/10/97 - 2/3/98; M 5 (Box 13)
  - Misc. Medical School Departments, 2/9/98 - 8/12/98; M 5 (Box 13)
  - Misc. Ad-Hoc Organizations, *9/6/94 only; O 1 (Box 13)
  - Misc. Ad-Hoc Organizations, 9/12/97 - 3/6/98; O 1 (Box 13)
  - Misc. Ad-Hoc Organizations, 3/18/98 - 8/31/98; O 1 (Box 13)
  - Council of Competitiveness, 9/5/1997 - 8/25/98; O 1.2 (Box 13)
  - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), 34500; O 2.11 (Box 13)
  - Education Groups, 9/2/97 - 3/11/98; O 3 (Box 13)
  - Education Groups, 3/12/98 - 6/22/98; O 3 (Box 13)
  - Education Groups, 6/23/98 - 8/31/98; O 3 (Box 13)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Ed. (COFHE), 9/16/97 - 12/23/97; O 3.1 (Box 13)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Ed. (COFHE), 1/8/98 - 3/24/98; O 3.1 (Box 13)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Ed. (COFHE), 4/29/98 - 7/20/98; O 3.1 (Box 13)
  - California Academy of Sciences, 10/3/97 - 8/25/98; O 3.2 (Box 13)
  - Consortium of Social Science Association (COSSA), 9/23/97 - 8/3/98; O 3.3 (Box 13)
  - Association Pacific Rim University, 4/21/97 only!; O 3.4 (Box 13)
  - American Adademy of Arts and Sciences, 10/1/97 - 6/2/98; O 3.7 (Box 13)
  - American Council on Education, 9/24/97 - 8/31/98; O 3.8 (Box 13)
  - National Assocation of Independent Colleges & Univ., 9/9/97 - 7/27/98; O 3.10 (Box 13)
  - College Entrance Exam Board, 10/3/97 - 5/15/98; O 3.25 (Box 13)
  - Aspen Institute, 10/30/97 - 8/28/98; O 3.37 (Box 13)
  - Institute of International Education (IIE), * 5/7/93 From: Wally Falcon/RE: Vision Statement; O 3.38 (Box 13)